

# Walidulhasan Boniamin

Full Stack Software Developer

Seasoned, Forward-Looking Software Developer with 3+ years of Background in creating and executing innovative software solutions to enhance business productivity. I can utilize my pre-existing skills in software development, database management, business intelligence, and software quality Assurance and gain experience working as part of a team. I always look forward to working on challenging and growth Oriented projects that allow enriching my skills in research and software development.

$\bowtie$	walidulhasanboniamin@gmail.com	L +8801735538903
2	Dhaka, Panthopath	www.twitter.com/walidulhasan
	www.github.com/walidulhasan	www.twitter.com/walidulhasan
å	https://bd.linkedin.com/in/walidulhasan-boniamin-57b611138	www.youtube.com/@bdcoders

### AREAS OF EXPERTISE

Software Development Lifecycle

**Technical Process Improvement** 

Web Application Design & Development

SQL Server Database Management System

**Project Management** 

**Digital Marketing** 

### WORK EXPERIENCE

### Software Developer

Robintex Group Bangladesh Limited

11/2021 - Present

#### Garments ERP

- A Complete ERP solution for garments company with different analytical reports.

### **Garments HRM System**

- HRM System having employee profile, attendance, leave & salary modules.

#### Gate Control System

- A system for controlling the product's entry & exit for both security & financial aspects.

### Officer

Agrani Bank Ltd

03/2018 - 05/2019

#### General Banking

Account opening /FDR/ABS/CD/ SB/ join CD/ST sb Bill taking -Current Bill, Telephone Bill Check Book Register Entry Payment of Allowance-Adult allowance, Poor & Disabled Data Entry Money Transfer & Money collection from other Bank,

### TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages : C# | JavasScript | TypeScript | Dart | SQL | HTML | XML | LinQ

Database : SQL Server

Frameworks : Entity FrameWork Flutte ASP.NET

Library : JQuery Bootstrap 5 Tailwind CSS

Reports : Crystal Report | RDLC | HTML Report

Version control: GitHub TFS

# **PROJECT**

### Library Management System

This application was created using WPF Form Tools, Dot.net Framework, and C # language in MS Visual Studio 2019

### Multi Group Chat App

Tools & Technology: HTML5, CSS3/4, BootStrap, Node.Js, jQuery,Npm

### HR Management System [Employee]

Tools & Technologies Used: Windows Form Application, DotNet Framework, bunifu framework, Ado.net, Partial View, SQL server 2019, Crystal Report, and MS Visual Studio 2019

#### Online Courses Buy and Sell Like Udemy

Tools & Technologies Used: Asp.Net Web Form, Ajax, JavaScripts, Bootstrap 4.6, Authentication and Authorization, Crystal Report, SQL Server 2019 and MS Visual Studio 2019

#### Asp.net mvc core application crud operations

Tools & Technologies Used: Asp.Net MVC Core V5.0,Ajax,JavaScripts, Bootstrap 4.6,Authentication and Authorization, Entity Framework code first approach ,SQL Server 2019 and MS Visual Studio 2019

### **CERTIFICATES**

Computer Fundamental (03/2021)

US Software Ltd

Mobile Application Development (03/2022)

Mobile App Development Project – ICT Division

Digital Marketing (03/2018)

Ledp Project - ICT Division

Office Application (03/2016)

College Program - Nazrulislam Institute

# **AWARD**

Ledp Best Freelancer Award in Bhola District

03/2019

### **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

# College Annual function

Volunteer

2 Times (2018-2019)

# **EDUCATION**

### Professional Diploma in IT, Enterprise System Analysis & Design with C# /.Net(11/2021)

IsDB-BISEW IT Scholarship Project (Islamic Development Bank-Bangladesh Islamic Solidarity Educational Wakf) Duration of the Course: 1 Year (1150 Hours)

### Bachelor of Arts (B.A) in English Literature (02/2019)

National University – (Bhola Govt. College)

Duration of the Course: 4 Years

### LANGUAGE

<u>Bengali</u> <u>Er</u>	<u>nglish</u> <u>K</u>	<u>(orean</u>
--------------------------	------------------------	---------------

writing: \*\*\* Writing: \*\*\*

Reading: \*\*\*

Reading: \*\*\*

Listening: \*\*\*

Listening: \*\*\*

### REFERENCES

### Md.Asadul Hoque

Jr.Vice President Head of Dept. IT & MIS Robintex Group Bangladesh LTD (+88) 01819815699 nipu@robintexbd.com

### Syed Zahidul Hassan

Consultant (.NET)
IsDB-BISEW IT Scholarship Program
Show & Tell Consulting Ltd
(+88) 01817015015
zahid@showtellconsulting.com



Walidulhasan Boniamin